Guide to the Mandy Carter Papers, 1970-2013 RL.00195
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Organizations and Projects Series, 1972-2006, 130 boxes
  - Ad Hoc Committee for an Open Process Subseries, 1998-2000, 1.5 boxes
    Includes communications, such as emails, letters, and faxes; notes from meetings and conference calls; prepared letters and statements, including drafts; media clippings; and files related to meetings in Boston, New York, and Pittsburgh.
    - Ad Hoc Committee files (Box 34-35)
  - Floridians Representing Equity and Equality Subseries, 1993-2000, 7 boxes
    Floridians Representing Equity and Equality (FREE) was an organization founded in 1997 and based in Tampa, Florida, that rolled out a statewide educational campaign to stop an anti-affirmative action ballot measure. Carter served as Campaign Manager from February 2000 to July 2000.
    Includes public relations materials, such as flyers, pamphlets, reports, media packages, press releases and speaker requests; contact lists; and correspondence, including emails and faxes. Also includes a set of chronological folders that document Carter's activities and meetings on behalf of FREE, including preparations for the March on Tallahassee. The chronological files often include correspondence leading up to a meeting or event, notes from it, and other related materials. A list of these folders can be found in the Gigs and Events Series.
    Carter spent the second half of 2000 in Florida working for Florida Vote/Equal Voice. As a result, materials related to each are sometimes interfiled, as are materials related to the Gore 2000 campaign.
    - FREE files (Box 25-28, 60-61, 68, 95)
  - Florida Vote/Equal Voice Subseries, 2000-2001, 3 boxes
    Florida Vote/Equal Voice was a non-partisan voter education, voter registration, and voter participation program that focused on Florida's African American communities. The campaign was initiated by the African American Ministries Leadership Council of the People for the American Way Foundation and the Florida State Chapter of the NAACP. The campaign was run in conjunction with Arrive With Five, a statewide voter mobilization program. Carter served as Campaign Manager from August 2000 to December 2000.
    Includes communications, such as emails and faxes; contact lists; program descriptions; schedules; profiles of target counties and cities; press clippings; and campaign materials and ephemera. Also includes a set of chronological folders that document Carter's activities and meetings on behalf of Florida Vote/Equal Voice, which typically contain correspondence leading up to a meeting or event, notes from it, and other related materials. A list of these folders can be found in the Gigs and Events Series.
    Carter spent the first half of 2000 in Florida working for Floridians Representing Equity and Equality. As a result, materials related to each are sometimes interfiled, as are materials related to the Gore 2000 campaign.
    - Florida Vote/Equal Voice files (Box 61, 66-67, 95)
  - Freedom to Marry Project Subseries, 2001-2002, 6 boxes
    Based in Boston, Massachusetts, the Freedom to Marry Project was a marriage equality organization founded by civil rights attorney Evan Wolfson. Carter served as a consultant to the organization from September 2001 to January 2002.
    Includes training manuals, contact lists and reports, research files on related organizations and efforts, meeting and phone call notes, emails and other communications, testimonies in opposition to House Bill 3375, Carter's contract, and ephemera. Also includes a set of files which trace her meetings, activities and travels on behalf of the organization. These often include correspondence leading up to a meeting or event, as well as notes from it, and other related materials. A list of these folders can be found in the Gigs and Events Series.
    - Freedom to Marry Project files (Box 55-58, 79-80)
  - Southerners on New Ground Subseries, 1993-2006, 9 boxes
    Founded in 1993, Southerners on New Ground (SONG) is a membership-based organization that aims to build a progressive movement across the South by developing transformative models of organizing that connect race, class, culture, gender, and sexuality. Carter is one of six co-founders of SONG, along with Joan Garner, Pat Hussain, Pam McMichael, Suzanne Pharr, and Mab Segrest. Carter also served as Executive Director from 2003 to 2005.
    Includes meeting notes and notes from Board of Directors calls; to-do lists; annual reports; communications, especially emails; files related to fundraising and financials, including budgets and fund appeals; program reports; materials related to women's retreats organized by SONG; files related to particular projects, including ones in Mississippi and Kentucky; and issues of SONG Notes, the organization's newsletter.
    - SONG files (Box 31-32, 81-86, 237)
  - Old Lesbians Organizing for Change Subseries, 2002-2006, 2 boxes
    Old Lesbians Organizing for Change (OLOC) was founded in 1989 to confront ageism within communities and to build a support network for lesbians 60 and over. OLOC's 5th National Conference was held August 17-20, 2006, in Durham, North Carolina. Carter served as a member of the host committee and was primarily responsible for organizing volunteers. She was also a keynote speaker at the event.
    Includes materials related to planning the conference, such as correspondence, notes from meetings and phone calls, to-do lists, contact lists, files related to volunteers and scheduling, promotional pamphlets and flyers, and clippings. Also includes the conference program and other materials from the conference itself, as well as issues of Reporter, OLOC's newsletter.
    - OLOC files (Box 221-222)
  - National Black Justice Coalition Subseries, 2003-2004, 1/2 box
    Founded in December 2003, the National Black Justice Coalition (NBJC) is a civil rights organization dedicated to empowering black LGBT people and fostering equality by fighting racism and homophobia. Carter is a founding board member, and as of 2013, she serves on the Leadership Advisory Council.
    Includes materials from board meetings, such as agendas, notes, and budgets; and communications, such as email and memos. A majority of the materials relate to marriage equality, including press releases, statements, and fact sheets for a press conference on African American support for the issue.
    - NBJC files (Box 35)
  - Other Organizations and Projects Subseries, 1981-2005, 15 boxes
    Includes files related to other organizations and projects Carter was in contact with or collected materials about. In some cases, Carter was involved as a volunteer, though typically in a more limited way than organizations appearing as their own subseries.
    Materials vary, but folders often include promotional items, such as pamphlets and flyers, newsletters, reports and updates, and fundraising appeals.
    Arranged in batches alphabetically and described below in an integrated alphabetical list. Organizations A-P appearing in Boxes 75 through 78 remain in their original order; other folders were assembled during processing.
    Similar types of materials, including some from organizations listed below, can be found in a group of folders that include mixed materials from affinity groups in the Administrative Files Series.
    - Act Up, 1988 (Box 216)
    - Action, St. Louis, Mo., 1993-1994 (Box 78)
    - AFL-CIO, 1994 (Box 75)
    - AFL-CIO, 1998 (Box 78)
    - AIDS Community Residence Association, 1994 (Box 75)
    - AIDS related, 1994-1995 (Box 75)
    - All God's Children, 1996-1997, 2002, 6 folders (Box 216)
    - Alliance of Lesbian and Gay Organizations of West Virginia, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Alternative Resources of the Triad (ART), 1989-1990 (Box 96)
    - American Association of University Women, 1993 (Box 75)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1993-1995 (Box 75)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 96)
    - American Friends Service Committee, Jenie Hall Bridges Project, 1992-1994 (Box 75)
    - American Friends Service Committee, Lesbian and Gay Task Force, 1982 (Box 96)
    - Americans for Tax Reform, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Americans United for Separation of Church and State, 1994-1995 (Box 75)
    - Amnesty International, "Breaking the Silence", 1994 (Box 75)
    - Artists for a Hate-Free America, 1996 (Box 96)
    - ASA AIDS Service Organization (Box 75)
    - Astraea, 1995 (Box 216)
    - Atlanta March Committee, 1988 (Box 216)
    - Bay Area Career Women (BACW), 1981-1982 (Box 96)
    - Bayard Rustin Commemorative Alliance (BRCA), 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Bisexual related, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Black Buddies, 1991-1992 (Box 96)
    - Black groups, 1992-1993 (Box 78)
    - Black Lesbian Support Group (BLSG), 1994-1995 (Box 96)
    - Bookstores, 1993-1995 (Box 75)
    - Building Bridges--Southern Initiative, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Campaign 1995, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Campaign for Human Development, 1994-1995 (Box 75)
    - Campaign for Peace and Democracy, 1995 (Box 75)
    - Campaign to End Homophobia, 1992-1994 (Box 75)
    - Campfest, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Campus Organizing Project, 1995 (Box 75)
    - Campus Watch, 1988 (Box 216)
    - Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council, 1999 (Box 96)
    - Carolina Gay and Lesbian Association (CGLA), 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Carolina Theatre, Durham, N.C., 1994-1995 (Box 75)
    - Catholics for a Free Choice, 1994-1995 (Box 75)
    - CCCO: An Agency for Military Draft Counseling, 1991 (Box 96)
    - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1994 (Box 75)
    - The Center, Los Angeles, Calif., 1993 (Box 75)
    - Charlotte Interfaith Network for Gay & Lesbian Equality (C.I.N.G.L.E.), 1994 (Box 75)
    - Chicago Black Lesbians and Gays, 1995-1998, 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Citizen's Conference to Stop Gun Violence, 1994 (Box 75)
    - CLOSER, Asheville, N.C. (Box 97)
    - Coalition Against Poverty, 1994-1999 (Box 97)
    - Coalition on Human Needs, 1994 (Box 75)
    - College Democrats of America, 1995 (Box 75)
    - Columbia Human Rights Committee (Box 75)
    - Committee Seeking Equal Justice for the Minnesota Eight (Box 75)
    - Committees of Correspondence, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Community Connections, Asheville, N.C., 1989-1990 (Box 97)
    - Congressional Black Caucus, 1994-1995 (Box 97)
    - D.C. Coalition of Black Lesbians, Gay Men and Bisexuals, 1993-1995, 4 folders (Box 97)
    - D.C. Friends of NC, 2001 (Box 97)
    - D.C. Lesbians Against Racism Everywhere (DCLARE), 1994 (Box 75)
    - D.C. New Democracy, 1994 (Box 75)
    - D.C. Statehood, 1994 (Box 75)
    - DCABP, 1991 (Box 97)
    - Democratic Party, 1992 (Box 97)
    - Department of Political Science, Boston University, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Digital Queers (Box 76)
    - Direct Action for Rights and Equality, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Disability Action Center of Georgia (Box 76)
    - Donnelly/Colt Custom Printing (Box 76)
    - Durham People's Alliance, 1997-1998 (Box 216)
    - Dyke TV, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Equality Colorado, 1993 (Box 97)
    - Equality NC PAC, 1999-2000 (Box 97)
    - The Experience, 1995 (Box 76)
    - Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting (FAIR) (Box 76)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Racial and Economics Justice Program (Box 97)
    - Feminist Majority Foundation (Box 76)
    - Fight the Right Network: Youth and Education Working Group, 1995 (Box 97)
    - Fight the Right, Philadelphia, Pa., 1995 (Box 76)
    - First Tuesday Charlotte, 1990-1991 (Box 97)
    - Forging Alliances for Interracial/Interfaith Tolerance of Homosexuals (FAITH), 1994 (Box 76)
    - Foundations/Non-profits, 1993-1995 (Box 76)
    - Fourth Freedom Forum, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Fund for Democratic Elections, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Fund to End Gun Violence, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Gay and Lesbian Americans, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Gay and Lesbian Center, San Francisco Main Library (Box 76)
    - Gay and Lesbian Parents Coalition International, 1994, 2 folders (Box 76, 97)
    - Gay and Lesbian Switchboard of Charlotte (Box 76)
    - Gay and lesbian think tanks (Box 76)
    - Gay Games, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Gay groups, 1998-2001 (Box 78)
    - Gay Men and Lesbians Opposing Violence (GLOV), 1994 (Box 76)
    - Gay Olympics, 1981-1982 (Box 216)
    - Gay, Lesbian and Straight Education Network, Inclusivity Task Force, 1999 (Box 97)
    - Gay, Lesbian and Straight Teachers Network (GLSTN), 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 76, 97)
    - George Washing University, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Gertrude Stein Democratic Club, 1995 (Box 76)
    - GLAAD, 1990 (Box 97)
    - GLAAD of the National Capital Area, 1994 (Box 76)
    - The Gourmet Club, Columbia, S.C., 1990 (Box 97)
    - Greater Triangle Foundation, Leadership Triangle, 1991 (Box 216)
    - Groups, North Carolina (Box 217)
    - GROW, 1989-1990 (Box 97)
    - Guilford Alliance for Gay and Lesbian Equality (GAGLE), 1988-1990 (Box 97)
    - Highlander, 2005 (Box 216)
    - Honor Our Neighbors Origins and Rights, 1992 (Box 98)
    - Human Rights Project, Kansas, Mo., 1994, 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Humanitas (Box 98)
    - Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Institute for Gay and Lesbian Strategic Studies, 1996-1998 (Box 98)
    - Institute for Policy Studies, 1995 (Box 76)
    - Institute for Public Media Arts Summit, 1996 (Box 98)
    - Interfaith Coalition, 1995 (Box 98)
    - International Center for Peace and the Arts, 1988 (Box 98)
    - Interreligious Health Care Access Campaign, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Jobs with Justice, 1995 (Box 76)
    - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Justice for Janitors, 1995 (Box 76)
    - Kitchen Table Press, 1992-1994 (Box 98)
    - LAMBDA Legal Defense Fund, 2 folders (Box 76, 98)
    - League of Women Voters of Orange, Durham, and Chatham Counties, 2004 (Box 98)
    - Legacy Foundation, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Lesbian Agenda for Action, 1988 (Box 98)
    - Lesbian and Gay Community Center of Augusta, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Lesbian Community Project, Portland, Or., 1990 (Box 98)
    - Lesbian/gay groups, 1985-1988 (Box 78)
    - Library of Congress Gay, Lesbian of Bisexual Employees (GLOBE) (Box 76)
    - Listening Project, 1994 (Box 98)
    - LLEGO, 1993 (Box 98)
    - Logcabin Club (Box 76)
    - Love and Rage Revolutionary Anarchist Federation, Anti-Facist Working Group (Box 76)
    - LUNA, 1986-1989, 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Lyon-Martin Women's Health Services, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Maat Dompim: Womyn of Color Land Project, 1995 (Box 98)
    - Mama Raga (Box 98)
    - Manbites Dog Theatre, 1994 (Box 76)
    - March on Washington, 1993 (Box 76)
    - Mautner Project, Washington, D.C., 1994 (Box 76)
    - Men of All Colors Together, 1994 (Box 98)
    - Metro/D.C. Committee of Correspondence, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Metrolina Community Service Project, Charlotte, N.C., 1989-1990 (Box 98)
    - Metropolitan Community Church, Charlotte, N.C., 1996 (Box 98)
    - Mississippi Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1994 (Box 76)
    - My Sister's Place, A Battered Women's Shelter and Their Children, Washington, D.C. (Box 76)
    - NAACP, 1993, 1999-2000, 3 folders (Box 99)
    - Naiad Press, 1991 (Box 99)
    - The Names Project, 1994-1995 (Box 76)
    - NARAL (Box 99)
    - NARAL-N.C., 1994 (Box 76)
    - NARAL-N.C. Women of Color Reproductive Freedom Initiative, 1992 (Box 99)
    - NARAL-National, 1994 (Box 76)
    - Nation of Islam, 1994 (Box 99)
    - National Association of Black and White Men Together, 1992-2001, 3 folders (Box 99)
    - National Black Women's Health Project, 1993 (Box 99)
    - National Center for Lesbian Rights, Lesbians of Color Project, 1991-1993 (Box 99)
    - National Coalition for Black Lesbians and Gays (Box 99)
    - National Coalition of Black Gays, National Office, 1985-1986 (Box 99)
    - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (NCARL) (Box 76, 99)
    - National Council of Negro Women, 1994 (Box 99)
    - National Democratic Club, 1993 (Box 76)
    - National Education Association (Box 77)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF), 1988-2005, 10 folders (Box 104)
      See also the Gigs and Events Series for materials related to the annual NGLTF conference Creating Change.
    - National Gay Rights Advocates, National Coming Out Day (Box 99)
    - National Lesbian Political Action Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 99, 216)
    - National Minority AIDS Council, 1993-1995 (Box 99)
    - National Organization of Black County Officials, 1992-1993 (Box 99)
    - National Organization of Women (NOW), 1988-2001, 13 folders (Box 103)
      Includes North Carolina local, Southeast regional, and national materials. Additional materials can be found in the Gigs and Events Series.
    - National Organizations Responding to AIDS: Senate Briefing, 1995 (Box 99)
    - National Organizers Alliance, 1992-1998 (Box 77, 99)
    - National Rainbow Coalition, 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 99)
    - National Stonewall Democrats, Other LGBT/Dem Stuff, 1999-2001 (Box 99)
    - National Voting Rights Museum, 1995 (Box 76)
    - Native American Rights Fund, [1992?] (Box 100)
    - NetGALA, 1994 (Box 77)
    - New Party, 1994 (Box 77)
    - News of Wake Interfaith Peace and Justice Groups, 1994 (Box 77)
    - The Newsletter, 1982-1987, 2 folders (Box 216)
      Publication of the Triangle Area Lesbian Feminists (TALF). The bulk of the materials relate to its production and dissemination by volunteers.
    - NHCC, 1994 (Box 77)
    - North Carolina groups, 1998, 2000-2001 (Box 78)
    - North Carolina AIDS Service Coalition, 1989-1990 (Box 100)
    - North Carolina AIDS/HIV Update, 1989-1990 (Box 100)
    - NC Cares, 1995 (Box 216)
    - North Carolina Caucus on AIDS in the Black Community (NCCABC), 1989-1990 (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Coalition for Gay and Lesbian Equality (NCCGLE), 1989-1994 (Box 77, 100)
    - North Carolina Coalition for Gay and Lesbian Equality (NCCGLE), Homophobia and Human Rights in North Carolina, [1996?] (Box 217)
    - North Carolina Community Land Trusts, 1994 (Box 77)
    - North Carolina Editorial Forum, 1994 (Box 77)
    - North Carolina Federation of Campus Gay and Lesbian Organizations, 1988, 2 folders (Box 100)
    - NC Forum, 1990 (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Political Action Agenda (NCLGPAA), 1991-1992, 8 folders (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Lesbian Gay Health Project (LGHP), 1989-1994, 2 folders (Box 76, 100)
    - NC Pride PAC, 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 217, 280)
    - North Carolina State University, 1994 (Box 77)
    - North Carolinians Against Racist and Religious Violence, 1987, 1989-1990, 3 folders (Box 100)
    - Northern Virginia Gay and Lesbian Coalition, 1995 (Box 77)
    - Northwest Coalition Against Malicious Harassment, 1993-1994 (Box 77)
    - Northwest Speak Out Project, 1995 (Box 77)
    - NOVA Pride, 1994 (Box 77)
    - Older Women's League Campaign for Women's Health, 1993 (Box 101)
    - Olivia, 1993-1995 (Box 78)
    - Our Own Place, Durham, N.C., 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Pamphlets, 1990s (Box 78)
    - Pamphlets, New England organizations, [1990s?] (Box 217)
    - Pamphlets, Religious and LGBT organizations, 2000 (Box 217)
    - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), 1991, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), 1995 (Box 78)
    - People's Alliance, 1990-1995 (Box 78, 101)
    - Perspectives on Diversity Video Distribution Project, 1998 (Box 217)
    - PFLAG, Interfaith Task Force, 1994 (Box 78)
    - PFLAG, Project Open Mind, 1995 (Box 217)
    - PFLAG, Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 78)
    - Philadelphia Lesbian and Gay Task Force, 1994 (Box 101)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1995 (Box 78)
    - Political Research Associates, 1994-1995 (Box 78)
    - Project South, 1994 (Box 78)
    - Queen City Friends, 1989 (Box 101)
    - Radical Women, 1994-1999 (Box 101)
    - Rainbow Coalition, California Civil Rights Initiative, 1994-1995 (Box 75)
    - Rural Southern Voice for Peace NC, 1994 (Box 101)
    - SC Pride, 2002 (Box 280)
    - Service Members Legal Defense Network, 1994-1995 (Box 101)
    - Sexual Minority Youth Association League (SMYAL) (Box 101)
    - SIECUS Community Action Kit, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Softening the Stone Twin Oaks (Box 101)
    - Sojourner & Associates, 1994 (Box 101)
    - Southern Appalachian Lesbian and Gay Alliance (SALGA), 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Southern Political Report, 1995 (Box 101)
    - Southern Poverty Law Center, 1995 (Box 102)
    - Southerners for Economic Justice, 1994 (Box 101)
    - Southwest Organizing Project, 1993-1994 (Box 102)
    - Speak Out!, San Francisco, Calif. (Box 102)
    - Stole Project, 1997 (Box 217)
    - Time Out Youth, Charlotte, N.C., 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Triad Health Project, 1994 (Box 102)
    - Triangle Area Lesbian Feminists (TALF), 1985-1988, 8 folders (Box 102)
    - Triangle Black and White Men Together, 1990 (Box 102)
    - Triangle Coalition of Black Lesbians and Gays (Box 102)
    - Triangle Foundation, 1999-2001 (Box 102)
    - Triangle Lesbian Gay Alliance, 1987 (Box 102)
    - Umoja, Durham, N.C., 1992, 1994 (Box 102)
    - Umoja, St. Louis, Mo., 1994 (Box 102)
    - Union Institute Center for Women, 1994-1995 (Box 102)
    - United States Conference of Mayors, 1993-1994 (Box 102)
    - United States Student Association (USSA), 1994-1995 (Box 102)
    - Unity Fellowship, 1994 (Box 102)
    - US Department of Labor, Women's Bureau, 1997-1999 (Box 217)
    - US Holocaust Museum, 1993, 1995, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Vets of Color, 1993 (Box 102)
    - Victory Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 102)
    - Virginians for Justice, 1994 (Box 102)
    - Whitman-Walker Clinic, 1994-1995 (Box 102)
    - Women's Project, 1992, 1994 (Box 102)
    - Women's Spirituality Forum, 1991, 1993 (Box 102)
    - Women's Sports Foundation, 1999 (Box 102)
    - Women's Trust Fund (Box 102)
    - WOW, Charlotte, N.C., 1990-1991 (Box 102)
- Gigs and Events Series, 1979-2013, 108 boxes
  A day-by-day account of Carter's work as a multi-issue activist, this series includes files documenting her speaking engagements and attendance at conferences, rallies, marches, retreats, meetings, and other types of gatherings.
  Materials vary, but files typically include correspondence, such as emails, faxes, and memos leading up to a meeting or event; promotional materials, including mailings, advertisements, and clippings; items from the event itself, such as notes, schedules, meeting agendas, and information packets; as well as LGBT publications and pamphlets for local, related, or attending organizations. Occasionally, outlines or the full text of speeches are included. Materials that were weeded during processing include travel receipts and reimbursement forms, travel documents and tickets, area maps and brochures, and national news publications.
  Arranged chronologically, with materials related to preparations for an event filed according to when the event occurred. For the most part, original order has been maintained, though many of the files from the 1980s and early 1990s were brought together during processing. Original folder titles have been retained, though loose materials were foldered and given titles following conventions established by Carter.
  There is significant overlap with the Organizations and Projects Series. Some materials filed here are related to organizations represented in the Organizations and Projects Series, and some of the files listed here are physically filed within the Organizations and Projects Series to maintain original order.
  - Speeches, undated (Box 218)
  - Gigs, 1990-1991 (Box 218)
  - Speeches: Mandy, 1990-1992 (Box 218)
  - Mandy's Speeches, 1991, undated (Box 218)
  - Speaking Gigs, 1991-1993, 5 folders (Box 218)
  - Requests: Gigs, Field Organizing, 1993 (Box 218)
  - Gigs, 1993-1998 (Box 218)